Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Subject Files
2.1.4.3
Marist College
  Box 1570 - Box 1576
- Subject Files, 2.1.4.3
  Box 1577
- Subject Files, 2.1.4.3
  - Subject files: Personalities: Political Figures, undated; 1 (Box 1577)
    - [Lowell Thomas preparing a broadcast with Nelson Rockefeller], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a man (Mayor LaGuardia?)], 2
    - Note [LT w/ Mayor LaGuardia], 3
  - Subject files: Personalities: Sports Figures, undated; 2 (Box 1577)
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting with Jim Thorpe at a table], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting with Branch Rickey], 2
    - Note: [Branch Rickey head of Brooklyn Dodgers], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting with sports figures], 4
    - Note: [LT, Hugh O'Brien, Mohammed Ali], 5
  - Subject files: Quaker Hill, undated; 3 (Box 1577)
    - [People dancing at Quaker Hill Country Club], 1
    - Note [Lowell Thomas Hammersley Hill Pawling, N.Y. 12564. Make a copy], 2
    - [People standing on a balcony at Quaker Hill Country Club], 3
    - Note [Quaker Hill Country Club], 4
    - Note [look for the pictures or have a print made], 5
  - Subject files: Chip Rafferty, undated; 4 (Box 1577)
    - [A little shrine ?], 1
    - [Chip Rafferty], 2
    - Note [Chip Rafferty. Australian movie actor. LT did 2 or 3 independent productions in Australia, New Guina (not High Adventures)], 3
    - [Various photos of Lowell Thomas], 4
    - [Various photos of Lowell Thomas], 5
    - [Various photos of Lowell Thomas], 6
    - [Various photos of Lowell Thomas], 7
  - Subject files: Edward V. "Eddie" Rickenbacker and James H. "Jimmy" Doolittle with Lowell Thomas, undated; 5 (Box 1577)
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with Edward V. "Eddie" Rickenbacker and James H. "Jimmy" Doolittle], 1
  - Subject files: John Roberts, circa 1950s; 6 (Box 1577)
    - [Crowded street], 1
    - [People walking on the street], 2
  - Subject files: Nelson Rockefeller, undated; 7 (Box 1577)
    - [Lowell Thomas and Nelson Rockefeller looking over a broadcast], 1
  - Subject files: Norman Rockwell, undated; 8 (Box 1577)
    - [Lowell Thomas with Norman Rockwell and another man], 1
  - Subject files: Franklin Delano Roosevelt, 1938; 9 (Box 1577)
    - [Lowell Thomas and Franklin Delano Roosevelt], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with Franklin Delano Roosevelt], 2
    - Note: Pawling, New York. News Commentator Lowell Thomas, is very informally clad, for his presidential audience. He is pictured in bathing shorts as he chats with President Franklin D. Roosevelt on the occasion of the latter's visit to Pawling, New York to watch Lowell's "Nine Old Men" play White House correspondents in a baseball game, 3
    - Note: If so, he seems to have gotten over it rather quickly. Maybe we could take a look at these together., 4
    - Note: Wide World Photo: Lowell Thomas, Senator James J Pope, and President Roosevelt after a softball game between The Nine Old Men and The New Deal Purgers", 5
  - Subject files: Theodore Roosevelt, Jr., Mrs. Roosevelt and Mr. and Mrs. Lowell Thomas, undated; 10 (Box 1577)
    - [Portrait of Mr. and Mrs. Lowell Thomas with Theodore Roosevelt, Jr., and Mrs. Roosevelt.], 1
  - Subject files: Sahuaro Ski Club, undated; 11 (Box 1577)
    - [Sahuaro Ski Club], 1
    - [Sahuaro Ski Club], 2
    - [Sahuaro Ski Club], 3
    - [Sahuaro Ski Club], 4
    - [Sahuaro Ski Club], 5
    - [Sahuaro Ski Club], 6
    - [Sahuaro Ski Club], 7
    - [Sahuaro Ski Club], 8
    - [Sahuaro Ski Club], 9
    - [Sahuaro Ski Club], 10
    - [Sahuaro Ski Club], 11
    - [Sahuaro Ski Club], 12
    - [Sahuaro Ski Club], 13
    - [Sahuaro Ski Club], 14
    - [Sahuaro Ski Club], 15
    - [Sahuaro Ski Club], 16
    - [Sahuaro Ski Club], 17
  - Subject files: John P. Sawyer, circa 1960; 12 (Box 1577)
    - [Woman stannding outside], 1
  - Subject files: Willy Schaefler, undated; 13 (Box 1577)
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a man], 1
  - Subject files: Shah of Iran, Reza Pahlavi, circa 1970s; 14 (Box 1577)
    - [Photo of Lowell Thomas with the Shah of Iran, Reza Pahlavi], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas with the Shah of Iran, Reza Pahlavi], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with the Shah of Iran, Reza Pahlavi], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas and Reza Pahlavi, the Shah of Iran], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas and te Shah of Iran, Reza Pahlavi], 5
  - Subject files: Skiing, circa 1970s; 15 (Box 1577)
    - [Photos of Lowell Thomas and his skiing friends], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and Marianna Munn Thomas], 2
    - [Marianna Munn Thomas], 3
    - [Thomas and other man skiing], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing with his friends], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing], 9
    - [Photos of Lowell Thomas skiing with his friends], 10
    - [Photos of Lowell Thomas skiing with his friends], 11
    - [Photos of Lowell Thomas with the Olympic trophies], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas receiveing presidential medal], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas receiveing presidential medal], 14
    - [Photos of Lowell Thomas and friends skiing], 15
  - Subject files: Skiing, undated; 16 (Box 1577)
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing with friends including Christl Thalhammer and Alf Engen, 1
    - [Lowell Thomas with man at Toni Matt Ski School], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing with man], [green tinted color negative], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting with woman at ski resort], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas, Tay Thomas, Lowell Thomas, Jr., and others at table at ski resort], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas, Tay Thomas, Lowell Thomas, Jr., and others at table at ski resort], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas, Tay Thomas, Lowell Thomas, Jr., and others at table at ski resort], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with woman on skis], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with woman on skis], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with woman on skis], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas leaning on fence at ski resort with three other men including Alf Engen], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing], 15
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing], 16
    - Note (applies to items 12-16): Negs - skiing - Baniff - Durrance, 17
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing with Christl Thalhammer], 18
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing], 19
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing with Alf Engen], 20
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing with Alf Engen], 21
    - Note (applies to items 18-21): Skiing, Alta, for Christl book?, 22
    - [Man skiing], 23
    - [Man skiing], 24
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jr. in military uniform with cactus], 25
    - [Lowell Thomas holding Shortee-skis], 26
    - [Woman on skis], 27
    - [Woman on skis], 28
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing], 29
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing], 30
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing], 31
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr., at Hammersley Hill in ski gear], 32
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr., at Hammersley Hill in ski gear], 33
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing with friends], 34
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing with friends], 35
    - [Portrait of Lowell Thomas with snowflake sweater], 36
    - [Lowell Thomas doing a radio broadcast surrounded by a group of people], 37
    - [Lowell Thomas, Lowell Thomas Jr., and other men surrounding a CBS microphone], 38
    - [Lowell Thomas doing a radio broadcast surrounded by a group of people], 39
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing with friends], 40
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing with friends], 41
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing with friends], 42
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing with friends], 43
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing with friends], 44
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing with friends], 45
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing with friends], 46
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing with friends], 47
    - Note (applies to items 40-47): Vail with Blanche & Dick Hausserman etc., 48
    - [Woman skiing, Christl Thalhammer?], 49
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing with friends], 50
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing with friends], 51
    - Note (applies to items 53-60): Alta sking [instructions for negatives], 52
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing], 53
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing], 54
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing], 55
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing with friends], 56
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing], 57
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing], 58
    - [Lowell Thomas with man at Toni Matt Ski School], 59
    - [Lowell Thomas with man at Toni Matt Ski School], 60
    - Note (applies to items 62-63): Mr. John Ryer Pawling, New York, 61
    - [Lowell Thomas with man at Catamount Ski School], 62
    - [Lowell Thomas with man at Catamount Ski School], 63
    - Note (applies to items 65-70): Hack Miller negs, best are loose, 64
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing with friends], 65
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing with friends], 66
    - [Woman skiing], 67
    - [Woman skiing], 68
    - [Woman skiing], 69
    - [Woman skiing], 70
    - Note (applies to items 72-73): Skiing Sun Valley, 71
    - [Lowell Thomas and four other men doing a CBS broadcast], 72
    - [Lowell Thomas and four other men doing a CBS broadcast], 73
    - [Lowell Thomas doing a radio broadcast surrounded by a group of people], 74
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing], 75
  - Subject files: So Long Until Tomorrow, undated; 17 (Box 1577)
    - [Man standing on an airplane], 1
    - [A group of monks (?)], 2
  - Subject files: Softball, circa 1930s; 18 (Box 1577)
    - [Group of softball players], 1
    - [Group of softball players], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with fellow softball players], 3
    - Note [Negatives of pictures used in softball/baseball scrapbooks], 4
    - [Nine Old Men softball team member up at bat], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas and his softball team (?)], 6
    - [Group photo of softball players and their wives (?) a women's team?], 7
    - [Softball player], 8
    - [Man up at bat, Lowell Thomas is the catcher], 9
    - [The Nine Old Men softball team], 10
    - [Man with flag watching a softball game], 11
    - [Members of a softball team], 12
    - [Members of a softball team], 13
    - [Man up at bat at a softball game], 14
    - [The Nine Old Men softball player sliding to base, 15
    - [The Nine Old Men softball team in the outfield], 16
    - [Two players on The Nine Old Men softball team], 17
    - [Man swining the bat, Lowell Thomas is the catcher], 18
    - [Men playing softball], 19
    - [Players on The Nine Old Men softball team with others], 20
    - [Softball players sitting in front of a car (with FDR?)], 21
    - [Two men in hats at a softball game], 22
    - [Softball players], 23
    - [Softball team], 24
    - [Players on a softball team], 25
    - [Group picture of a softball team], 26
    - [Players on a softball team], 27
    - Note [Oysters + Nine Old Men], 28
  - Subject files: Softball, circa 1930s; 19 (Box 1577)
    - [Softball players with bats], 1
    - [Man hitting a softball], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a General Douglas MacArthur], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas hitting a softball], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas and Colonel Stoopnagel in a baseball hat witing something], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas and others watching a softball game], 6
    - [The Nine Old Men softball team], 7
    - [Group picture of the Debtors and Creditors], 8
    - [Photo of a softball team], 9
    - [Group picture of the Debtors and Creditors and the CBS softball team], 10
    - [Men dressed as women? Softball team?, including Lowell Thomas, Jr.], 11
    - [Group photo of a softball team], 12
    - [Members of a softball team], 13
    - [Men dressed as women? Softball team?, including Lowell Thomas, Jr.], 14
    - [Spectators of a softball game], 15
    - [Group photo of a softball team], 16
    - [Spectators at a softball game], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas with Franklin Delano Roosevelt at a softball game], 18
    - Note (applies to items 20-25): Roosevelt-softball, 19
    - [Photos of Franklin Delano Roosevelt attending a softball game], 20
    - [Photos of Franklin Delano Roosevelt attending a softball game], 21
    - [Photos of Franklin Delano Roosevelt at a softball game], 22
    - [Photos of Franklin Delano Roosevelt at a softball game], 23
    - [Teddy Roosevelt, Jr. and Billy Van impersonating Franklin Delano Roosevelt], 24
    - [Teddy Roosevelt, Jr. and Billy Van impersonating Franklin Delano Roosevelt], 25
    - Note (applies to item 27) [Paul Parker Photo New York City], 26
    - [Lowell Thomas dressed up for indoor softball game], 27
    - [Lowell Thomas in the Nine Old Men softball uniform with a man in a turban (another softball player?)], 28
    - [Teddy Roosevelt, Jr. and Billy Van impersonating Franklin Delano Roosevelt], 29
    - [Teddy Roosevelt, Jr. and Billy Van impersonating Franklin Delano Roosevelt], 30
    - Note (applies to item 31): [Negative T. Roosevelt. Billy Van], 31
    - [Teddy Roosevelt, Jr. and Billy Van impersonating Franklin Delano Roosevelt], 32
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking hands with a woman at a softball game], 33
    - [The Nine Old Men versus The New Deal Purgers], 34
    - [Lowell Thomas with members of his softball team (?)], 35
  - Subject files: South Pole, 1962; 20 (Box 1577)
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking a man's hand from a plane], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and two other men in the South Pole, 2
    - [Lowell Thomas and two other men in the South Pole], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas with three men in the South Pole], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with two others in the South Pole], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking hands with a man from a plane], 6
  - Subject files: Staff, 1961; 21 (Box 1577)
    - [Lowell Thomas and two men looking over papers], 1
  - Subject files: Silas Strawn tribute, circa 1968; 22 (Box 1577)
    - [Painting of Silas Strawn], 1
    - [Painting of Silas Strawn], 2
    - [Painting of Silas Strawn], 3
    - [Framed tribute to Silas Strawn], 4
    - [Framed tribute and painting to Silas Strawn], 5
  - Subject files: Erling Strom, undated; 23 (Box 1577)
    - [Erling Strom and three others standing in the snow], 1
    - Note [Leudley (?) in checkered shirt, Strom next, Like(?) and Pearson on the end. At 11,000 elevation Mt. ME (?) expedition May 1932], 2
    - [Man in a snowsuit on skis], 3
    - Note [Erling Strom at Base camp on Cache Creek (lost..?) of 4,500 elevation. Mt. McKenley (?) expedition. April or May 1932], 4
    - [Man on skis in beneath of snowy mountains], 5
    - Note [Erling Strom (?) at 7,200 elevation (?) Mt. McKenley expediation April + May 1932], 6
    - [Erling Strom and two others at camp], 7
    - Note [Strom in middle, Leik on right, and Pearson on left at Base Camp 4,500 elevation at the finish of the tub (?). Mt. McKenley Expedition April and May 1932], 8
    - [Erling Strom's base camp during Mt. McKenley expedition], 9
    - Note [Erling Strom at 11,000 ft camp. Biglee (?) fall in background. Muldrow (?) glaciers. Mt. McKenley expedition. April to Mayn 1932.], 10
    - Note [LT Nite], 11
    - [Photos from a banquet event with Erling Strom (?)], 12
    - [Photos from a banquet with Erling Strom(?)], 13
  - Subject files: Sultan of Perak, Malaya, 1921 - 1922; 24 (Box 1577)
    - [Lowell Thomas with the Sultan of Perak], 1
  Box 1578
- Subject Files, 2.1.4.3
  - Subject files: Christl Thalhammer, circa 1963; 1 (Box 1578)
    - [Christl Thalhammer], 1
    - [Christl Thalhammer with a Native American man], 2
    - [Christl Thalhammer], 3
    - [Christl Thalhammer], 4
    - [Christl Thalhammer in a bathing suit], 5
    - [Christl Thalhammer], 6
    - [Christl Thalhammer], 7
    - [Christl Thalhammer], 8
    - [Christl Thalhammer], 9
    - [Christl Thalhammer], 10
    - [Photos of Christl Thalhammer], 11
  - Subject files: Christl Thalhammer, circa 1963 - 1964; 2 (Box 1578)
    - [Christl Thalhammer, Lowell Thomas, and another man on skis], 1
  - Subject files: Christl Thalhammer, Adventures with the New Guinea Headhunters, 1965; 3 (Box 1578)
    - [Man speaking with tribespeople in New Guinea], 1
    - [Man speaking with a group of tribeswomen in New Guinea], 2
  - Subject files: Kurt Thalhammer, undated; 4 (Box 1578)
    - [Kurt Thalhammer and another man carrying skis], 1
  - Subject files: Lowell Thomas (alone), circa 1960s; 5 (Box 1578)
    - [Lowell Thomas standing outside a house], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas standing in front of a "No Parking Here" sign], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas in a studio], 3
  - Subject files: Lowell Thomas (alone), circa 1960s - 1981; 6 (Box 1578)
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with two men], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas], 3
    - [Portrait of Lowell Thomas], 4
    - [Sketch of Lowell Thomas], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas tipping his hat], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas tipping his hat], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas tipping his hat], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas tipping his hat], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas tipping his hat], 10
    - [Portraits of Lowell Thomas], 11
    - [Portraits of Lowell Thomas], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas ?], 13
  - Subject files: Lowell Thomas (portraits) [color], 1979 - 1981; 7 (Box 1578)
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting outside], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting outside, tipping his hat], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas], 3
  - Subject files: Lowell Thomas (publicity photographs), circa 1950s; 8 (Box 1578)
    - [Lowell Thomas on a boat in icy water], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas on a boat in icy water], 2
    - [Portrait of Lowell Thomas], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting at a desk], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas in Washington D.C.], 5
    - [Portrait of Lowell Thomas], 6
  - Subject files: Lowell Thomas (publicity photographs - Morocco), 1958; 9 (Box 1578)
    - [Portrait of Lowell Thomas in Morocco], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas in Morocco], 2
  - Subject files: Lowell Thomas (miscellaneous photographs), undated; 10 (Box 1578)
    - [Lowell Thomas writing at camp], 1
    - [Man in a furry hood], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. with other members of the Explorers Club], 3
    - [Two men (the Wright Brothers?) working on a plane], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a man by a "No Parking Here" sign], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas patting a man on the shoulder], 6
    - [Three people standing in front of a plane], 7
    - [Sign for 'Romantic India" at the Philharmonic Hall], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas with other people riding on an elephant], 9
    - [Man being carried], 10
    - [Two people in the ruins of a building], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas and captains gathered around a table], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas and two men by a camera], 13
    - [People standing on a patio], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas talking with Eddie and General Doolittle.], 15
    - [Men on horses], 16
    - [Lowell Thomas and Nelson Rockefeller going over a script], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas and Nelson Rockefeller going over a script], 18
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with two men], 19
    - [Lowell Thomas in a car with a man and woman], 20
  - Subject files: Lowell Thomas, Jr., 1930s - 1960s; 11 (Box 1578)
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. standing on suitcases], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. getting into a plane], 2
    - [Pilots (?)], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. in uniform with two dogs], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr.with his teammates], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. holding fish, standing with a girl], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas and others in uniform], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. petting a dog], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr.], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. with a woman, 10
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. with a dog on a leash], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. standing in the garden], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. wearing a hat], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. giving a speech], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. cheering at a podium], 15
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. delivering a speech], 16
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. on a ship], 17
    - [Map of South America with the route of the U.S.S. San Francisco. "Around Cape Horn"], 18
    - [Certificate for Lowell Thomas Jr.], 19
  - Subject files: Mostyn Thomas (opera singer), undated; 12 (Box 1578)
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with Mostyn Thomas], 1
  - Subject files: Tibet, 1949; 13 (Box 1578)
    - [Lowell Thomas with two men and a donkey in Tibet], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas with two men and a donkey in Tibet], 2
    - [Man rowing a boat in Tibet], 3
    - [A house with yaks in Tibet], 4
    - [Live production in Tibet], 5
    - [Walking along a mountain pass in Tibet], 6
    - [A klarge building on top of a mountain in Tibet], 7
    - [A man with two dogs in Tibet], 8
    - [A shrine (?) in Tibet], 9
    - [Monks in Tibet], 10
    - [Marketplace (?) in Tibet], 11
    - [Mother and child in Tibet], 12
    - [Man painting in Tibet], 13
    - [Two women and a man sitting in Tibet], 14
    - [A group of people eating in Tibet], 15
    - [Monks in Tibet], 16
    - [City in Tibet], 17
    - [A group of monks in Tibet], 18
    - [A Tibetan monk standing in front of an ornate door], 19
    - [Monks standing outside in a city in Tibet, 20
    - [Painting on a wall in Tibet], 21
    - [A group of Tibetan monks tanding outside], 22
    - [Tibetan monks], 23
    - [Three Tibetan children], 24
    - [The Dali Lama (?) in Tibet], 25
    - [The Potala Palace on top of a hill in Tibet], 26
    - [The Potala Palace in Tibet], 27
    - [Tibetan monk], 28
    - [Tibetan monks], 29
    - [The Dali Lama in Tibet (?)], 30
    - [Performers in Tibet], 31
    - [A performer in Tibet], 32
    - [Performers in Tibet], 33
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a man in Tibet], 34
    - [Lowell Thomas riding a donkey in Tibet], 35
    - [Lowell Thomas looking at the mountains in Tibet], 36
    - [LowellThomas looking down at the Potala Palace (?) in Tibet], 37
    - [A group of men on donkeys walking through the mountains in Tibet], 38
    - [Lowell Thomas receiving papers from a man in Tibet], 39
    - [A man and a donkey walking on a pathway in the mountains of Tibet], 40
    - [Travelers taking a break on the road in Tibet], 41
    - [Man sitting in a field in Tibet], 42
    - [Two Tibetan men], 43
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with two men in Tibet], 44
    - [The mountain trail and a river in Tibet], 45
    - [Tibetan men carrying wooden platforms (?) on their backs], 46
    - [Man next to a building in the mountains of Tibet], 47
    - [Building in the mountains of Tibet], 48
    - [Man walking with a donkey in Tibet], 49
    - [Man riding a donkey with supplies through the mountains of Tibet], 50
    - [Lowell Thomas on a horse in Tibet], 51
    - [Lowell Thomas riding a horse in Tibet], 52
    - [Unloading supplies from donkeys in Tibet], 53
    - [Men walking towards a building in Tibet], 54
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. looking at a map of South America], 55
    - [Tibetan man looking at a map], 56
    - [Men on donkeys on a trail through the mountains of Tibet], 57
    - [Two men unloading supplies from donkeys in Tibet], 58
    - [Lowell Thomas receiving something from a man in Tibet], 59
    - [Lowell Thomas, holding cloth, with two other men holding a sack and meat], 60
    - [Lowell Thomas standing next to a man in Tibet], 61
    - [A line of men on horses in Tibet], 62
    - [Line of horses and donkeys walking through a river in Tibet], 63
    - [A donkey carrying supplies in Tibet], 64
    - [A building on a hill in Tibet], 65
    - [A city in Tibet], 66
    - [Rock walls in Tibet], 67
    - [Lowell Thomas and others on horses in Tibet], 68
    - [A Tibetan city by the water], 69
  - Subject files: Tibet, 1949; 14 (Box 1578)
    - [Donkeys in Tibet], 1
    - [Man walking towards a building in Tibet], 2
    - [Donkeys by a rock wall in Tibet], 3
    - [Three men outside a city in Tibet], 4
    - [Two Tibetan woman preparing food], 5
    - [Tibetan children playing], 6
    - [Tibetan person doing farmwork], 7
    - [Tibetan woman carrying something on her back], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas and his caravan traveling through Tibet], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas on a horse walking through a river], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas's group traveling through Tibet], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas's group traveling on a road through the mountains of Tibet], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas at the base of a mountain in Tibet], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas riding a horse through the mountains of Tibet], 14